Sometimes You Have to Fall Before You Fly
Full Out is a history, drama, family film directed by Sean Cisterna.
Based on the true life story of California gymnast Ariana Berlin.
As she zoned in on her Olympic goals, 14 year old Ariana Berlin's life took a
sharp turn when she was involved in a debilitating car accident.
Gaining her confidence and movement back through learning hip hop dance, she unexpectedly found herself
called back to the gymnastics world thanks to world renowned UCLA Coach Valorie Kondos Field.
With Val's help, Ariana was eventually able to secure a spot on the UCLA gymnastics team and
win an NCAA championship, a lifelong goal that she had always dreamed of.
This is a wonderfully inspiring story of persistence, confidence, and the
heart and courage to make a somewhat impossible comeback in life.
Ariana Berlin, played by Ana Golja.
Coach Valorie Kondos-Field, played by Jennifer Beals.
Michelle, played by Asha Bromfield.
Nate, played by Trevor Tordjman.
Coach Pierce, played by Jake Epstein.
Susan Berlin, played by Ramona Milano.
Full Out, also known as Full Out: The Ariana Berlin Movie, is a 2015 drama young-adult TV movie
directed by Sean Cisterna based on the life story of American gymnast Ariana Berlin.
Ana Golja received a 2016 Canadian Screen Awards nomination for Best
Performance in a Children's or Youth Program or Series.
The film explores themes of dancing, sports,
gymnastics, biography, car accident.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.